Hello Hello Friends Welcome to Online
Assistant Seedhi Baat No Bakwas
[Music]
So friends
a lot of information videos keep coming on Online Assistant YouTube channel
and we always keep bringing new videos
which are on different topics, if you
want you can go to the video playlist and
watch the entire playlist here,
apart from that you
can search for videos from here, on the real side it is
seen that on whichever topic you
want to search the video, you
can simply type here, so friends
in today's video I am going to talk about that
many times we have to get hospitalized
which involves huge expenses and a lot of
payments which are medicine bills
and apart from that a lot of hospital expenses have to be
presented in the safe and
due to the hospital bills we have to
face a huge financial officer, so today
in this video I will tell you
how you can
avail the benefit of hospital cash insurance with the help of Paytm, it is very
institution based in which you have to pay one thousand
or 2000 as per the type of land you
use  According to that, you
get the benefit per day. So friends,
if you are using ATM, then simply
open your Paytm app. If you have
not installed Paytm app in your mobile,
then you can search it from Google Play Store and
install it from the link given in the description. So the interface of Paytm app has been
made very user friendly.
Simply you have to keep scrolling down.
When you scroll down a little,
here you will see a section
of insurance.
After reaching there, you will have to click on view all. When you
click on it, an interface will appear like this. After
reaching here, you will see Tailormade Products Powered by 197 Communication Limited. After reaching here,
you have to click on the seal. When you click on the seal,
some similar interface will appear.
After reaching here, you will
get the option of hospital cash insurance.
Tap on it. If you tap on it, then
information comes in front of you in this way. The
plan is of chapters.
Additionally, in this you get fixed reimbursement for the
number of countries,
for whichever country, that is, maximum 15 days, 30 days, 45
days, according to the maximum you use,
you get ₹1000 for 15 days,
15-9-2016, let us talk about the last
₹5000, here you
get the benefit, if you
use a plan of ₹1000 per day, then
its premium for one year will be
Rs.255 plus GST, you will see the land details below,
here it is completely digital, this
policy is completely digital, it
is covered in the existing basis, hospital Delhi cash benefit up to 50 days, that is,
if you have to be hospitalized in the hospital for 30 days continuously, then
you can get a help of ₹1000 per day here,
if
you remain hospitalized here for more than 30 days, then you will get a
maximum of 30 days  You will get the benefit of only Rs. 1000 per day and if
you stay for two days within one to three days,
you will
get Rs. 1000 per day as per the clamp here. If
you click on the terms and conditions, then
its terms here are simple,
you can see here that the policy is
only for Indian citizens who are
Paytm users. Each policy is
for people between 18 to 50 years of age, which is
for personal income tax and the
inception of the policy is that the age of 18
to 50 should be checked.
After taking the policy, the customer will have to
wait for the working day, then your policy will be
activated, that is, transaction
plus waiting period has been kept in its name.
This policy is provided to you here by ICICI
Lombard General Insurance Company
with Paytm.
Here you get to see another option
in which it is given to you that if you
take more than three policyholders, then
you will get a maximum of three  The only policy benefits you
can avail here are the Delhi Hospital Cash
Comforts, which you will get only after a minimum of 24 hours of
hospitalization.
If you are hospitalized for less than that,
you will not get the benefit. There is an initial waiting
period for the free dish,
which is 30 days. For example,
pre-existing diseases will be
covered after 30 days, but they will be covered.
[Music]
Similarly,
you will get to see all the information here. This is the
terms and conditions. Now here we will
see how to book it. The
plan we have chosen here is of
₹1000, its premium is 265
plus GST. In this way, if we look at 5000, then
you will have to pay 3814 as premium here.
If we
look at 2,000, then it is ₹500. In this way, you
can choose the plan according to your budget and then you will have to click on the field.
After clicking on the seat, you  The
information will automatically
pop up here and the details will be filled.
You will have to use the date of birth mainly.
You will have to add it here when you click on add new option. Here the
details of the added person
automatically pop up.
You have to choose the date of birth, so you have to
select it and come down.
After coming down, you have to add it by playing add new option here.
After that, if you
want, you can fast-forward here in
which payment is made from Paytm wallet.
We will turn it off
because we do not have money in our Paytm wallet. If you
click on premium
here, then you will have to pay 255 plus GST i.e. total
₹300 here.
After coming to the payment page, you will see that the
balance in our Paytm wallet is only 14, so we
cannot make payment through it. Then you will have to
select the new payment option.
Payment can be made through debit and credit card,
UPI through net banking and
even PM IAS.  If you want to pay the bill,
you can do it simply through UPI
and here you will have to enter your UPI ID,
now when you enter that UPI ID, your UPI ID will be displayed here and
then you will have to click on Pay Now
when you click on it, the
app whose address you have given here,
if done on the phone, will open here.
Now
see, the payment has popped up on our phone,
now here you will have to simply
click on Pay After clicking on Pay,
you will have to click on Proceed here and
after that you will have to make a payment of ₹300 from your concerned account
here.
To make the payment, you will have to do the UPI ledger here
and after that
you will receive an SMS of your difference copy
and a PDF file will be delivered to your email,
after that you can print that copy and
keep it with you or you
can save it and if needed,
you can
avail the benefit of your hospital cash insurance through it,
so friends, let's go home.
You must have liked the video. If you liked the video then
please like, share and comment. We will meet you
with some other such video. Till then, Eid Jai
Hind Jai Ho.